So here we go with the second half.
Yay!
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm so happy.
Please do.
So, I have a favor to ask you,
I heard that you are good at Othello,
That's right.
I would be happy if you could play with me today.
Please do.
Really?
I have written "Othello" in my profile, but I have never played against him before.
I see.
I've never played against idols like this before, so this will probably be my first time.
Yay!
I look forward to working with you.
Do you have any special skills?
Yes, I do.
I play Othello on my cell phone app in my free time,
I played too much.
I got the hang of it and it's now my special skill.
Amazing!
You're so cool!
I'm pretty confident this time.
I used to play Othello with my grandfather when I was little,
That's so cute.
I'll do my best not to lose.
Please do.
Thank you for watching.
Wow, that's great! I want to do my best. It's a special skill of mine.
I see. It was written in the book.
I want to win right away.
I'd like to win right away.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors-paper.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors.
Aiko, aiko, aiko, aiko, aiko, aiko, aiko, aiko, aiko, aiko, aiko, aiko.
Which is better?
I wonder which is better.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors first.
But we have to line up.
Well, which is better?
Either one is good.
Black, then?
Yes, black.
Wow.
Okay, I'll go.
I'm white, right?
White.
Yes, sir.
Wow, this brings back memories.
I don't know where I'll go.
You have a knack for this.
I didn't know.
Oh, I can't put it down.
It's a skill.
Oh.
Yes, sir.
Okay, here.
Oh.
I see.
You're like a master at this.
By the way.
Do you have any idea what you can do to win?
If I do this, I can win.
If I do this and get a card, I can win.
I see.
But I understand that.
I understand.
How much contact do you usually have with the members?
I don't contact them at all.
I see.
I don't have a lot of LINE connections.
That's a little bad.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I said I'm good at it.
I see.
You do?
Yes, I do.
What do you talk about?
Recently, there's a member named Ruri Aoi.
We've been talking about having a girls' night out with her.
What do you mean?
Well...
We're going on an expedition, and we're going to stay here for a long period of time.
Away from home.
And we'll be staying there for a few nights.
What do you call it?
You know the Hotel Girls Club?
Let's do that.
A girls' night out.
We're making plans now.
I'm making plans.
How nice!
What should we do?
Oh, that...
I think I'll stay here.
Yes, I think so.
It's nice.
But Miyu is the one I talk to the most.
Like on LINE.Like a line.
I don't know, he likes uniforms.
I told him I wanted to go out with him in uniform, and he said yes.
So I bought some uniforms.
I wanted to see it.
Where are you going?
We were talking about doing company activities.
Company activities?
I heard it's called "photography.
This is the first time I've heard of it.
It's really cool, isn't it?
So...
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait!
Wait.
They ran out of black.
Black is gone.
Maybe I'm not good at Othello anymore.
Not at all.
Why?
Play it again, please.
Please.
But you know what?
It's something I remember.
It was memorable.
That first time, you lose everything.
Shall I change the color?
Can I change it to white?
I've only ever bought in white.
Really?
Yes.
Then maybe when you're choosing a color...
Which do you prefer?
After you.
After you?
White.
Yes, sir.
I see.
Thank you very much.
I see. I don't contact you much, do I?
That's right.
Do you have a group line?
Is there a group line?
Yes, there is.
Who starts the conversation?
Mon-chan?
Is that right?
Mon-chan usually says something interesting in this video,
Or a clip from TikTok?
Mon-chan usually reports to me that this video is interesting, or that there was a girl who used the soundtrack,
I see.
Who's going to talk about it?
I'm Ayame.
Ayame-chan. What do you mean?
Well, unexpectedly, we talk about live performances and so on,
I often talk about live performances and things like this.
Serious stuff.
That's right.
Or, sometimes, when they talk about something like, "This is not a live concert, but what should we do?
Director-chan replies.
Heh~.
Yes, that's right.
Do you go out to dinner? Member: Yes, I do.
Member: Yes, we do. Maybe.
If I have a chance.
But I think Rine and I go most of the time.
Rinemin mostly.
Would you like to have the three of us together?
Two at a time.
That's what you mean. Like a duo.
Not a duo. Fair.
I see.
Rine asks me to go out with her,
So it's easy for me to ask her out.
Because I know her.
Even the members?
I don't know. I think about it too much.
I wonder if I should tell them.
I wonder if I'm not telling them.
It's surprising, isn't it?
When I ask a member out once, it's fine,
But if I ask a few times, I wonder if it is too much for them. I think that's unexpected,
Surprisingly, I was fine with Riichan and the others I mentioned earlier.
I thought what if they thought I was too much of a bother to ask them out,
But that didn't happen.
Ruri is a very thoughtful person, isn't she?
Yes, she is. You're handing out gummy bears, aren't you?
That's right.
She is a good communicator,
But both of the new members are very good at that,
I can feel it.
So I think it's good.
I am quite shy.
I see. I don't have an image of you at all.
Really?
We're still talking about it.
Wait. I'll get up.
I got the first card.
This is big.This is big.
This is quite a way to look at it.
I see.
What do you do about MCs?
What about the MC?
Is there someone in charge of MC?
We discuss it together,
The tour is divided into two groups, Generation-chan and Hisa-chan.
We are divided, aren't we? Invitation.
That's right.
Oh no.
I'm sorry. He let me play the first round every time just now.
That's great.
I see.
You're talking to No. 4?
It's like that.
And you drink water while you're talking,
How do you decide what to do?
In our case, the six of us talk together,
On tour, the member in charge of the show decides,
Usually it depends on the show,
Usually, it depends on the show, but on tour, it is often decided by all the members or a large group,
And since there are 9 of us, I wonder who decides the winners?
I wonder who decides the winners.
When do you decide?
It's usually right before the concert.
It's the same.
I'm glad.
So that's why you push.
Is that what you mean?
That's why they push it.
But you know what? Recently,
We talk among the members.
When we are on tour, we have a time to talk about it,
So, while I was young.
We take a break.
But recently,
Not recently,
A lot of people have started Instagram, haven't they?
Yes, they have.
Did you have a reason to start?
A lot of members.
Were you like an interviewer?
Thank you very much.
Was there a trigger?
A trigger.
We all did what we wanted to do when we wanted to do it,
And when we realized it, everyone was doing it.
When Uka started,
One of us started, and we all wanted to do it,
I was wondering if it was okay to do it. I was like, "Is it OK to do it?
So I was holding it back.
So, I wonder how it will turn out. I don't know.
That's probably how it was.
Everyone timed it well,
Like on their birthdays.
I see. I see.
Miyu was really confused about the timing,
She said she wanted to make it an anniversary or something.
Yes, yes.
You were watching the video, weren't you?
I watched a lot.
I mean, I watched it.
I see. Miyu wants to meet you.
Really?
She's always nervous about meeting you.
I don't know...
It's really mutual,
Like the day we send each other LINE messages,
Once a week or something,
That's right.
We've had some sudden conversations that have fallen by the wayside,
Please get to know each other.
I'm really shy,
I've been a member of Staff Run for 18 years,
Miyu is the only friend I've ever talked to,
That's so nice.
I'm sure that's true. That's why,
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I see.
I want him as a friend.
Ayume is a good friend of mine,
She seems to get along well with our members and is not very shy,
But the other members don't say anything about it either.
Surprisingly, I don't have shyness,
So, how do you enjoy it?
I guess that's true.
Especially at events like the Stuffala festival,
I feel like I have a strange face.
But Yuna and Ruri went out for dinner,
I didn't know that. I didn't know that.
I didn't know that until the story was published.
You call them Lurigumi?
I called them Lurigumi.
I call them Luli-chan,
I call them Lulipio,
I think there are people who call me Lurigumi.
Why is that?
I was Lurigumi from the beginning.
Really?Really?
You have a strong image of gummy bears, don't you?
That's right. I was given gummy bears when I first met you.
I see. That's how I became a Gummi.
Maybe that's how you became Gumi-chan.
That's right.
I'm sorry. I'll take it off.
Wow!
It's true.
That's right.
Wait!
This feels good.
But on the other hand, I can't put it here.
Really?
I can put it here?
Yes, you can.
Four more to go.
Who's game?
Hello?
We were playing, weren't we?
You won.
Yes, sir. Thank you very much.
When Uka and I played,
We were a team, Uka, as a group,
I see. So it wasn't a showdown or anything.
Yes, that's right. It was a showdown with another group,
I thought that Higashiura-san was doing the same thing.
Really? That's amazing.
Let's battle.
It's possible, isn't it?
Isn't it difficult?
It is difficult, isn't it?
I'm watching strategy videos.
Wait. First time.
Last gasp.
Thank you.
Yes, I did.
I gave it to you.
That's great.
Yay!
I don't know how to get the edges.
Can I ask you a trick?
Taking the edge,
You have to make white here before two of the four,
If it were me, I wouldn't be able to make white here.
I can only put black here,
I would have to make this my color,
And the two previous ones must also be my color,
If the two previous ones are white, I can't put white here, can I?
So that's how it is.
I'm going to make this and that my own color,
Here, here, and here.
That's right. But in terms of order,
Take here,
Here, here, here, and here,
here, and here.
I've heard good things.
Before you know it.
But if IT takes it,
Like I said before.
I don't know what's going on,
I took as much as I could first.
I lost.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for a wonderful time.
I lost.
Next time notice
Halo Pro Trainees
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
Please come again next time.
Please come again when we both know the tricks of the trade.
Please come again by all means.
Thank you very much.